<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tutorials on Everyone Program: A free, self-paced, coached introduction to computer programming for people who know nothing about it.</title>
    <link>http://everyoneprogram.com/tutorials/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tutorials on Everyone Program: A free, self-paced, coached introduction to computer programming for people who know nothing about it.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://everyoneprogram.com/tutorials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tutorials</title>
      <link>http://everyoneprogram.com/tutorials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://everyoneprogram.com/tutorials/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here are the three free online tutorials we&amp;rsquo;ll be using. They are all chosen to
ease you into programming in the gentlest way possible. There&amp;rsquo;s no rush &amp;ndash;
you&amp;rsquo;ll work at whatever pace you&amp;rsquo;re most comfortable with, and during the
meetings we&amp;rsquo;ll have one or more coaches available if you get stuck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To get you going in the easiest way possible, we&amp;rsquo;ll start with
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.codecademy.com/learn/learn-python&#34;&gt;CodeAcademy&amp;rsquo;s Learn Python&lt;/a&gt;. This
requires no setup at all, and will quickly show you what programming feels
like.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next you&amp;rsquo;ll get a bit more depth with &lt;a href=&#34;https://learnpythonthehardway.org/python3/&#34;&gt;Learn Python the Hard
Way&lt;/a&gt;. Don&amp;rsquo;t be fooled by the
title &amp;ndash; it&amp;rsquo;s actually one of the easier introductions to the language.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally you&amp;rsquo;ll work your way through the &lt;a href=&#34;https://tutorial.djangogirls.org/en/&#34;&gt;DjangoGirls
Tutorial&lt;/a&gt; and learn to build a
programmable web site. This tutorial is legendary for its friendliness and
simplicity. The lessons in the tutorial also include links to associated
videos.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At this point we can direct you to further learning resources depending on
your interests; for example you might want to start programming MineCraft or
explore the &amp;ldquo;Internet of Things&amp;rdquo; using MicroPython. Or you might have a special
project you&amp;rsquo;d like to tackle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>